It will be held till Diwali,
from today's Diwali till the coming Diwali and this
pick is such a pick that you can invest in it with great confidence,
very strongly and very confidently, you
can stay invested and
maintain the investment because from the
price at which this stock is standing now,
it will only move sideways,
so there is no question of a downside, I do
n't see anything like that because
it is well below its fresh value and their market is very strong,
their market is very strong, in this excuse also
their client base is also very strong, they are keeping
their own clients
and attracting new clients
and they are working very strongly in their field,
I think in their own way
they are like a leading and a leader, hence
you should definitely make a deal in this living insurance company,
this deal should definitely be in your portfolio,
ICICI Home Guard
for its 12 month target of 1870, my
comment to you would be that you should definitely make a buy in this, a
strong deal, a jam-packed deal, a fun deal
and a trustworthy deal with great confidence, it
has the capability to take all the dons of the market to jail and the price is  That price
is much lower than its residual value so buy
ICICI Lombard for target of 1870
buy ICICI Lombard good deal strong deal
and very good deal